<!-- Plugin Configuration File. Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-configuration-file.html -->
<idea-plugin>
    <!-- Unique identifier of the plugin. It should be FQN. It cannot be changed between the plugin versions. -->
    <id>com.txl.hosts</id>

    <!-- Public plugin name should be written in Title Case.
         Guidelines: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/marketplace/plugin-overview-page.html#plugin-name -->
    <name>Hosts</name>

    <!-- A displayed Vendor name or Organization ID displayed on the Plugins Page. -->
    <vendor email="tong.xl@outlook.com">tongxiaolong</vendor>

    <!-- Description of the plugin displayed on the Plugin Page and IDE Plugin Manager.
         Simple HTML elements (text formatting, paragraphs, and lists) can be added inside of <![CDATA[ ]]> tag.
         Guidelines: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/marketplace/plugin-overview-page.html#plugin-description -->
    <description>
        This plugin offers a seamless interface for managing and configuring hosts directly within the Maven tab of your IDE. With a user-friendly layout, it helps developers efficiently manage multiple host configurations without manual intervention.

        Key features include:
        - **Intuitive Interface Layout**: The plugin is integrated under the Maven tab, providing a clean layout. On the left side, you can view a list of hosts, while the right side displays detailed information for the currently selected host.

        - **Host Management**: Easily add, delete, or switch between hosts using the left panel. The plugin provides real-time viewing and editing capabilities for each host’s configuration.

        - **Automatic Configuration Storage**: The plugin automatically creates and manages host configuration files. If a configuration file doesn’t exist, it will generate and initialize it, ensuring all host configurations are properly stored and maintained.

        - **Convenient Operations**: Users can quickly access, add, and edit host configurations with simple clicks, eliminating the need to manually manage configuration files.

        This plugin is designed to boost your development productivity by streamlining the process of managing and switching between multiple host configurations.
    </description>

    <!-- Product and plugin compatibility requirements.
         Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-compatibility.html -->
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <!-- Extension points defined by the plugin.
         Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-extension-points.html -->
    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">

    </extensions>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <toolWindow id="Hosts"
                    factoryClass="com.txl.hosts.HostsToolWindowFactory"
                    anchor="right"
                    icon="META-INF/pluginIcon.svg"
                    />
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>